Welcome to the night, the cards laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secret sun fall
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
We are Kangol
Betrayal
A mirror's edge and the heart's parade
You true your truth and
Symbols bleeding through
Lost taste
Sweet but
You ready for the prophecy?
I hope you know Sanskrit.
If you know Sanskrit, you'll be okay.
If you don't know Sanskrit, you'll probably be kind of confused.
It's okay. You can learn Sanskrit.
It's not too late.
Okay.
I have to get this out.
For the guys that mad at me, they asked me to say this one thing.
They asked me to say one thing.
I have sex.
You're right.
What did you want me to say you want me to say one thing? Can you just put on the screen, please?
Okay
Ma nikia vidnam upala
yayan team
ma dalasam manjula
bagi salim
Mahendra
Rani dhiyuti ko mangalam matakhyangam manasas marami
Chaturbudje chandrakalavutamse kuconatase kum kum maragosone
Matta, Malakatsamya, Matang, Madalasini, Kuryayataksharasam, Kalayam, Karambavam, Asani.
Java matangya ne ya ya nitto pala jute
Jaya sanghuta skrathe, Jaya ila skruthe
Jaya janani sudas samudra
Ranta jyamun mani vapasim rudyate
Viravam tabidya malakam phavuruma
Call upon school to learn my Canton Alba Seasal Priyay.
Kritav Priyay, Sarvalokatav Priyay.
This is too much for me, I can't speak.
This language guy is a little bit too much. That was all I could do that was that was
It goes on for a thousand at least hundred pages. I can't do any more than that
I'll finish it off
Sarvara varni ke Sarva Mantra Mickey Sarva Yantra Mickey Sarva Tantra Mickey Sarva Chakra Matrikay Sarva Saka
kya thamike, sarva fitumike, sarva vedimike, sarva vidyamike, sarva yogatmike, sarva vanaratmike, sarva ghitmike, sarva nadritmike, sarva sadmukke, sarva visadubike, sarva vagramutmike, sarva savarinupike, sarva sarva ruppe, yagamike, sarva savarinupike, sarva savarinupike, sarva savarinupike, sarva savarinupike, sarva savarinupike, sarva savarinupike, sarva savarinupike, sarva savarinupike, sarva savarinupike, sarva savarinupike, sarva savarinupike, sarva savarinupike, sarva savarinupike, sarva savarinupike, sarva savarinupike, sarva savarinup
Trakiyee, pahi mam, pahi mam, pahi mam
Devi tu bhyam namo, devi tu bhyam namo, devi tu bhyam namo, devi tu bhyam namo, devi tu mam namaha
That's all I can do, guys.
It's too confusing past that part.
Are we at May? Do I have my slides already yet?
Hold on it's stuck I think
Okay, this is probably the end, guys.
I can finish one more hard watermelon.
Other than that, if it isn't, come on.
My buddy.
I have a buddy supposed to be helping me out.
My buddy's not helping me.
Buddy, his name is M-ANUS, and don't call him Anus.
Just call him Monus, okay.
Monus, my Indian guy.
Indian guy, we're from India.
You're like a smartest AI in the world, practically.
You can't make me a slideshow.
Manush?
Manush, I know you're really Manush.
I know you're not, but that's Manush, you're Manush.
Manush in India, I know.
I see, one, two, three.
Kalipriya Lane, OK?
I see it.
Okay, guys, that's enough. Okay. I can't take it anymore. I'm just gonna finish this lesson with my own nobody wants to talk
Nobody wants to say hi. No, we want to read you. What's the donate? Okay? I'm gonna let me send a leaf. I'm leaving
I'm ending this I'm ending this
Just a boil don't say the N word you better not say the N word. I'm telling spunky. I'm telling spunky
I'll play an outro video, but that's that's what you guys get
So no one's going to join no one would do anything. Okay. Bye. Yeah, true video. Bye
Bye
You and ghost with your halo
Airplane mode I felt it in my skin. So I was seen like design
And let a stranger's body keep me cool
you know the spark you know the gun you pull the string I come undone you say you love to watch me burn baby pay the only thing we've loved
Not to be celestial, but the way you left was biblical
So I did something ritual, cause grief for me is silicone
I might have sent a picture from a mortal bed
Just to haunt you goddamn head
I knew you crave the chaos I fed, cause love like all they never did
Not to be divine, but I love you
Even when I want to curse you, I could never rise
We trade halos for horns, it's fair
Every wound you gave, I wear
We take turns being the villains' muse
But damn it, I still wanna lose
Not to be celestial, but you made my claim perpetual
So I did something sexual, just to feel conceptual
I might've sent that photo from the strangers layer
not to be divine but i love you even when i want to cause you i could never
Don't forget what was never spoken
Every scar, a holy mark
Every kiss, another spark
Not to be divided